<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on jimmyff</title><link>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on jimmyff</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><copyright>© {year}</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 19:05:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frogger / Crossy road Playdate remake</title><link>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/2021-08-07-frogger/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 19:05:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/2021-08-07-frogger/</guid><description>I got super excited when the idea to make a frogger / crossy-road game for the playdate hit me. The crank would be perrrfect! I can imagine the frantic cranking as you try to rush in front of 4 lanes of traffic and a train!
I also figured it would be a fun project to learn Rust on. So without further adieu, behold&amp;hellip; the first thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made in rust!</description></item><item><title>Crypto Clock - the crypto currency ticker that runs on an old Kindle</title><link>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/2021-07-22-crypto-clock/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/2021-07-22-crypto-clock/</guid><description>(I&amp;rsquo;ve also posted this article over on Medium)
I had a special birthday coming up and I wanted to make a cool gift to mark the occasion. As the recipient is interested in crypto currencies &amp;amp; blockchain tech, I thought a desk/shelf crypto price ticker would be a cool present. I found a couple of products online but they were either not very good or prohibitively expensive so I decided to have a go at building one myself.</description></item><item><title>Painting asteroids</title><link>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/2021-07-16-painting-asteroids/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jimmyff.github.io/blog/2021-07-16-painting-asteroids/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been stewing on how I could fill the asteroids to make my space game look better. It&amp;rsquo;s a tricky problem as I only know terrain lines and nothing else (so I don&amp;rsquo;t know which side is supposed to be solid and which is supposed to be the empty void of space). This shows what I have and what I want to achieve:
I can trust that the space ship will always be in space (even if it&amp;rsquo;s hit an asteroid, it should never actually be in the asteroid!</description></item></channel></rss>