<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on jimmyff</title>
    <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on jimmyff</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© Jimmy Forrester-Fellowes</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Making Pride badges</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2022-08-05-making-pride-badges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2022-08-05-making-pride-badges/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to buy some progressive pride badges for this years pride so I turned to Etsy. I was pretty surprised at how much people were charging for them; £3.50 for a single badge. So classic me, I bought a badge making press!
I&amp;rsquo;ve had an awsome time desining and making loads of different badges! I was concious of not wanting to generate landfill so sourced eco-friendly components. Unlike most other badges, these use 100% degradable clear PLA disks over the artwork rather than conventional (cheaper) mylar plastic discs -which never degrade!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a sticker app in 5 days</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2022-07-08-building-a-sticker-app-in-5-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2022-07-08-building-a-sticker-app-in-5-days/</guid>
      <description>During London Pride I had a great selfie with some friends but the photo was spoilt by something in the foreground. I thought I&amp;rsquo;ll add a stiker over part of the photo so I turned to the Goolge play store to find an app. I quickly found that I was spoilt for choice but they were almost all terrible. Despite their quality the download numbers were mindblowing, some of the apps had tens of millions of downloads!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Play banned my highly rated app with no real justification</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-12-23-google-play-banned-my-highly-rated-app-with-no-real-justification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-12-23-google-play-banned-my-highly-rated-app-with-no-real-justification/</guid>
      <description>(I also published this article over at Medium)
Google Play&amp;rsquo;s Policy team is judge, jury and executioner. They didn&amp;rsquo;t give me a real explanation or even a chance to appeal their decision. I share my story in the hope that it reaches Google Play and they reevaluate and improve the way they handle cases like mine.
For the last few years I&amp;rsquo;ve filled my evenings and weekends building a fan app dedicated to the &amp;lsquo;Eurovision Song Contest&amp;rsquo; (an annual song competition), it&amp;rsquo;s been my little hobby/passion project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frogger / Crossy road Playdate remake</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-08-07-frogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 19:05:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-08-07-frogger/</guid>
      <description>I got super excited when the idea to make a frogger / crossy-road game for the playdate hit me. The crank would be perrrfect! I can imagine the frantic cranking as you try to rush in front of 4 lanes of traffic and a train!
I also figured it would be a fun project to learn Rust on. So without further adieu, behold&amp;hellip; the first thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made in rust!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Clock - the crypto currency ticker that runs on an old Kindle</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-07-22-crypto-clock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-07-22-crypto-clock/</guid>
      <description>(I&amp;rsquo;ve also posted this article over on Medium)
I had a special birthday coming up and I wanted to make a cool gift to mark the occasion. As the recipient is interested in crypto currencies &amp;amp; blockchain tech, I thought a desk/shelf crypto price ticker would be a cool present. I found a couple of products online but they were either not very good or prohibitively expensive so I decided to have a go at building one myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting asteroids</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-07-16-painting-asteroids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-07-16-painting-asteroids/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been stewing on how I could fill the asteroids to make my space game look better. It&amp;rsquo;s a tricky problem as I only know terrain lines and nothing else (so I don&amp;rsquo;t know which side is supposed to be solid and which is supposed to be the empty void of space). This shows what I have and what I want to achieve:
I can trust that the space ship will always be in space (even if it&amp;rsquo;s hit an asteroid, it should never actually be in the asteroid!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurovision game 2.0 - The card game!</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2020-12-21-eurovision-game-2-the-card-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2020-12-21-eurovision-game-2-the-card-game/</guid>
      <description>My previous Eurovision game took around two of prototyping countless versions and lots and lots of playtesting but I never felt I was tottally satisfied with it. About 6 weeks ago I started working on a tottally new reminaged game and today I&amp;rsquo;ve finally finished creating the first proper protoytpe complete with artwork. Read on to here about how it plays!
Game design Bringing some succesful parts of the previous game forward: There was a lot of really good stuff in the previous game so I brought forward the bits that I were portable and would fit in to this new game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a web app, the progressive way</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2018-06-25-building-a-web-app-the-progressive-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2018-06-25-building-a-web-app-the-progressive-way/</guid>
      <description>And finding an unconventional solution to a challenging objective
(I&amp;rsquo;ve also posted this article over on Medium.)
As a passionate developer I’m aways juggling side projects alongside my pay-the-bills work. Earlier this year I secured some great tickets to the Eurovision Song Contest and in the excitement I decided to build a modern web app to explore and discover the history of the annual show. I set myself some objectives:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The many beautiful worlds of Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2017-07-17-the-many-beautiful-worlds-of-cellular-automata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2017-07-17-the-many-beautiful-worlds-of-cellular-automata/</guid>
      <description>(I&amp;rsquo;ve also posted this article over on Medium.)
I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in Cellular Automata (such as &amp;lsquo;Conway&amp;rsquo;s Game of Life&amp;rsquo;) for years. I&amp;rsquo;ve implemented them countless times in various programming languages. A couple of weeks back I created a Dart library for exploring playing with Cellular Automata, it&amp;rsquo;s open source and available on Github. You can browse the demos on github or see the library running on my personal website -the gifs on this article were also generated using the library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
