<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>eurovision on jimmyff</title>
    <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/tags/eurovision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eurovision on jimmyff</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© Jimmy Forrester-Fellowes</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/tags/eurovision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Play banned my highly rated app with no real justification</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-12-23-google-play-banned-my-highly-rated-app-with-no-real-justification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2021-12-23-google-play-banned-my-highly-rated-app-with-no-real-justification/</guid>
      <description>(I also published this article over at Medium)
Google Play&amp;rsquo;s Policy team is judge, jury and executioner. They didn&amp;rsquo;t give me a real explanation or even a chance to appeal their decision. I share my story in the hope that it reaches Google Play and they reevaluate and improve the way they handle cases like mine.
For the last few years I&amp;rsquo;ve filled my evenings and weekends building a fan app dedicated to the &amp;lsquo;Eurovision Song Contest&amp;rsquo; (an annual song competition), it&amp;rsquo;s been my little hobby/passion project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurovision game 2.0 - The card game!</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2020-12-21-eurovision-game-2-the-card-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2020-12-21-eurovision-game-2-the-card-game/</guid>
      <description>My previous Eurovision game took around two of prototyping countless versions and lots and lots of playtesting but I never felt I was tottally satisfied with it. About 6 weeks ago I started working on a tottally new reminaged game and today I&amp;rsquo;ve finally finished creating the first proper protoytpe complete with artwork. Read on to here about how it plays!
Game design Bringing some succesful parts of the previous game forward: There was a lot of really good stuff in the previous game so I brought forward the bits that I were portable and would fit in to this new game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a web app, the progressive way</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2018-06-25-building-a-web-app-the-progressive-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyff.co.uk/blog/2018-06-25-building-a-web-app-the-progressive-way/</guid>
      <description>And finding an unconventional solution to a challenging objective
(I&amp;rsquo;ve also posted this article over on Medium.)
As a passionate developer I’m aways juggling side projects alongside my pay-the-bills work. Earlier this year I secured some great tickets to the Eurovision Song Contest and in the excitement I decided to build a modern web app to explore and discover the history of the annual show. I set myself some objectives:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
